Schaefer, Vincent; Papers ua902.010
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Atmospheric Sciences Research Center, 1950-1993; Undated; 6; 16.0 cubic ft.
  - Reports & Publications, 1948-1992; Undated; 6.7
    - "Catalyst: What's in a Cup of Coffee? Lots of Ideas for Science Experiments", V. Marteka (edited), 1975 January 31 (Box 26 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 29)
    - "Air Quality Observations in the Shawangunk Mountains," V.J. Schaefer, 1975 February 14 (Box 26 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 30)
    - "Solar Energy Experiments for Secondary School Students", Thomas W. Norton, Donald Hunter and Roger Cheng, 1975 February (Box 26 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 31)
    - "Preliminary Report of Air Quality Conditions in Capitol and Legislative Office Building Albany, New York," V.J. Schaefer- unpublished typescript, 1975 March 26 (Box 26 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 32)
    - "Scientific Adventures," V.J. Schaefer, 1975 March (Box 26 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 33)
    - "The Question of Acid Rain," V.J. Schaefer- manuscript, 1975 May 16 (Box 26 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 34)
    - "Particulate Measurements in the Office Area of Dr. Alfred Zamm", V.J. Schaefer- with letter, 1975 June 25; 1975 June 30 (Box 26 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 35)
    - "Antarctic Aerosols", Hogan, A.W, 1975 June (Box 26 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 36)
    - "Minimum Energy Building Solar Heated, Solar Energy for New York State," D.L. McClenahan, 1975 June (Box 26 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 37)
    - "A Trip on the Colorado Through The Grand Canyon," V.J. Schaefer, 1975 September 22-1975 October 08 (Box 26 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 38)
    - "The Developmental of Small Solar Heated Greenhouses in Regions Having Short Growing Seasons and Limited Water Supplies", V.J. Schaefer, 1975 October 01 (Box 26 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 39)
    - "More Heat From Your Fireplace", V.J. Schaefer- With supplementary materials, 1975 October; 1975 November (Box 26 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 40)
    - "Atmospheric Sciences Research Center SO2 Oxidation Rate in Plumes from Oil-Fired Power Plants- A Laboratory Study,"- Final Report, 1975 (Box 26 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 41)
    - "Air Quality in the Grand Canyon", V.J. Schaefer, 1975 (Box 26 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 42)
    - "The Effect on Air Quality of Wood Burning", V.J. Schaefer, 1975 (Box 26 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 43)
    - "Eighth Air Quality Reconnaissance Study of Northern Arizona and Southern Utah", V.J. Schaefer- typescript, 1975 (Box 26 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 44)
    - "Energy for Survival: The Alternative to Extinction", V.J. Schaefer, 1975 (Box 26 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 45)
    - "The Inadvertent Modification of the Atmosphere by Air Pollution," V.J. Schaefer, 1975 (Box 26 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 46)
    - "Investigation of the Pseudobinary Solid Solutions of AgI-CuI by Means of X-Ray Diffraction", H. Chession, R.E. Passarelli Jr. and B. Vonnegut, 1975 (Box 26 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 47)
    - "Preparation of a Position Paper on Inadvertent Weather Modification in Relation to the Space Shuttle Exhaust Products," V.A. Mohnen- Grant Proposals, 1975 (Box 26 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 48)
    - "The Foam Volcanos of the Bozenkill in the Helderhills," V.J. Schaefer, 1976 January 30 (Box 26 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 49)
    - "Atmospheric Sciences Research Center SO2 Oxidation Rate in Plumes from Oil-Fired Power Plants- A Laboratory Study", 1976 February (Box 26 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 50)
    - ASRC Report, D.C. Blanchard, L. Sikorowski, V.A. Mohnen and B. Vonnegut, 1976 September (Box 26 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 51)
    - "Physical Properties of the Atmospheric Aerosol," A. Hogan, 1976 September (Box 26 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 52)
    - "Minimum Energy Building: The First Winter's Operation," D.L. McClenahan, 1976 December (Box 26 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 53)
    - ASRC Report, 1976 (Box 26 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 54)
    - Final Report: "The Air Quality Patterns of Aerosols on the Global Scale," V.J. Schaefer- text, charts, measurements, figures, 1976 (Box 26 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 55)
    - "Global Patterns in Size and Number of Airborne Particles," V.J. Schaefer, ca. 1976 (Box 26 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 56)
    - "A New Method for Measuring Particle Concentration in a Cloud", V.J. Schaefer- with outline measurements, 1976 (Box 26 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 57)
    - "Routine Measurement of Submicroscopic Lead Particles in the Atmosphere and their Possible Role in Inadvertent Weather Modification", V.J. Schaefer, 1977 October (Box 26 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 58)
    - "Is Something Happening to Our Supply of Supercooled Clouds?" V.J. Schaefer, 1977 (Box 26 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 59)
    - "GASP Cabin Ozone Study," R. Falconer, 1977 (Box 26 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 60)
    - "Production of Air Bubbles of a Specified Size", D. Blanchard and L.D. Syzdek, 1977 (Box 26 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 61)
    - "Trace Gas and Fine Particle Measurements in Ireland", V.J. Schaefer- manuscript, 1977 (Box 26 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 62)
    - "A Trip on the Colorado Through the Grand Canyon", V.J. Schaefer- MNA/ASRC, 1978 September 22-1978 October 08 (Box 26 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 63)
    - ASRC Report, 1978 September (Box 26 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 64)
    - "Dry Ice=Antarctica", A.W. Hogan, 1978 Fall (Box 26 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 65)
    - "The Air Quality of Northwestern Montana", V.J. Schaefer- unpublished manuscript and typescript with map and measurements, 1978 (Box 26 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 66)
    - "The Presence of Ozone, Nitric Acid, Nitrogen Dioxide and Ammonia in the Atmosphere", V.J. Schaefer, 1978 (Box 26 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 67)
    - "The Use of Trace Gases and Submicroscopic Particles to Establish the Quality of the Global Atmosphere", V.J. Schaefer- manuscript, chart, article, measurements, 1978 (Box 26 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 68)
    - "Simple Experiments in Atmospheric Physics," V.J. Schaefer, 1979 June (Box 26 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 69)
    - "Notes on a Visit to Splot Pond and Mink Pond", V.J. Schaefer- manuscript, 1981 August 23 (Box 26 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 70)
    - "Twenty-Nine Days on Top of the Shawangunks: A Study and Measurement of Air Quality", V.J. Schaefer, 1981 November 10 (Box 26 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 71)
    - "Global Patterns in Size and Number of Airborne Particles", V.J. Schaefer and Atmospheric Aerosols and Nuclei, A.F. Roddy and T.C. O'Conner, 1981 (Box 26 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 72)
    - "The Problem of Acid Rain", V.J. Schaefer- manuscript and correspondence, 1981 (Box 26 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 73)
    - "Record of Some Experiments on Chemical Precipitation," A.W. Hogan, 1981 (Box 26 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 74)
    - "Twenty- Nine Days on Top of the Shawangunks: A Study and Measurement if Air Quality", V.J. Schaefer- unpublished manuscript and measurements, 1981 (Box 26 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 75)
    - "The Human Environment- Action or Disaster", V.A. Mohnen, 1982 June (Box 26 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 76)
    - "Investigation of Marble Deterioration of City Hall of Schenectady, New York," R.J. Cheng and R. Castillo, 1982 August 15 (Box 27 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 1)
    - "Estimation of Sulfate Deposition", A.W. Hogan, 1982 (Box 27 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 2)
    - "A Proposal for a Field Program for the N.Y.S. Museum and Science Service", V.J. Schaefer- typescript and draft, 1983 May 20 (Box 27 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 3)
    - "Thoughts Relative to the Need for a Training Program to Develop Competent Field Observers", V.J. Schaefer- typescripts and manuscript, 1983 June 01 (Box 27 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 4)
    - 36th Annual Gaseous Electrons Conference, 1983 October 11-1983 October 14 (Box 27 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 5)
    - "The Effect on Air Quality of Wood Burning," V.J. Schaefer- unpublished typescript, 1983 (Box 27 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 6)
    - "Some Characteristics of Chemical Precipitation", A.W. Hogan, 1983 (Box 27 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 7)
    - "Atmospheric Sciences: 25 Years Young," M. Fiess, 1986 Spring-1986 Summer (Box 27 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 8)
    - "Ubiquitous Geometry: Some Examples Showing the Significance of Size and Shape in the Works of Man and Nature", C.H. Bachman, 1988 September (Box 27 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 9)
    - "Serendipity and the Innovation", V.J. Schaefer, 1991 Fall (Box 27 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 10)
    - "The Modification of a Hurricane", V.J. Schaefer- unpublished manuscript, 1992 (Box 27 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 11)
    - "Air as a Natural Resource", V.J. Schaefer- manuscript, Undated (Box 27 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 12)
    - "Airborne Carbon Particles and Marble Determination," M. Del Monte, C. Sabbioni and O. Vittori, Undated (Box 27 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 13)
    - "Air Quality Considerations for Land Use Planning", V.J. Schaefer- unpublished typescript, Undated (Box 27 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 14)
    - "The Bounce Effect," K. Loomis, Undated (Box 27 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 15)
    - "Can Vegetable Productivity be Economically Increased in the Northeastern U.S.," V.J. Schaefer, Undated (Box 27 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 16)
    - China Lake Proposal/ China Lake, California- V.J. Schaefer (With photos), Undated (Box 27 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 17)
    - "A Classification for Gas to Aerosol Conversions," E.G. Walther- unpublished typescript, Undated (Box 27 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 18)
    - "The Cold Chamber as in Aid for Teaching and Conducting Research"- V.J. Schaefer, Undated (Box 27 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 19)
    - "Come in….Rain or Shine " Multiple Authors, Tributes to W.R. Whitney, Undated (Box 27 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 20)
    - "Contribution to the Growth of Ice Crystals Falling in Supercooled Water Cloud", J. Podzimek, Undated (Box 27 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 21)
    - "The Detection of Silver Iodide Nuclei by Their Effect on Ice Crystal Formation," V.J. Schaefer- manuscript, Undated (Box 27 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 22)
    - "The Detection of Very Small Amounts of Ozone and Nitrogen Dioxide Using a Gas-to-Particle Reaction", V.J. Schaefer- manuscript and correspondence, Undated (Box 27 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 23)
    - "The Development of Small Solar Heated Greenhouses and Related Techniques for Supplementary Food Supplies in Areas Having Short Seasons and Limited Water Supplies", V.J. Schaefer- correspondence, Undated (Box 27 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 24)
    - "The Discovery of a Practical Method for Producing Large Numbers of Ice Nuclei"- V.J. Schaefer- manuscript, Undated (Box 27 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 25)
    - "Energy Needs and the Atmosphere", W. Mordy, Undated (Box 27 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 26)
    - "Environment," V.J. Schaefer- manuscripts, Undated (Box 27 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 27)
    - "The Field Detection of Distant Sources of Gases and Fine Particles", V.J. Schaefer, Undated (Box 27 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 28)
    - "Field Observations of Thunderstorms," V.J. Schaefer- unpublished typescript, Undated (Box 27 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 29)
    - "Fiji," V.J. Schaefer- manuscript, Undated (Box 27 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 30)
    - "Fires," V.J. Schaefer- manuscript, Undated (Box 27 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 31)
    - "The Formation of Ice Crystals", U. Nakaya, Undated (Box 27 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 32)
    - "Forms of Water in the Winter Time", V.J. Schaefer- unpublished manuscript, Undated (Box 27 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 33)
    - "Growth and Development of Helogeistic Cross-Cultural Research," J.M. Schaefer, Undated (Box 27 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 34)
    - "The History of the Production of Artificial Fog", V.J. Schaefer- manuscript with calculations and photocopies), Undated (Box 27 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 35)
    - "How I Happened to be on the Canyon Trip", V.J. Schaefer- manuscript, Undated (Box 27 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 36)
    - "Ice Nuclei Concentrations at Mount Washington During Thirteen Years," Manuscript, V.J. Schaefer and H.G.S. Lanford, Undated (Box 28 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 1)
    - "Ice Nuclei Studies in Historical Perspective," Manuscript, V.J. Schaefer, Undated (Box 28 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 2)
    - "Ice River Relics," Typescript and Photos, V.J. Schaefer, Undated (Box 28 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 3)
    - "The Inadvertent Modification of the Atmosphere by Air Pollution," V.J. Schaefer, Undated (Box 28 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 4)
    - "Lead Particles," Manuscript Fragment, V.J. Schaefer, Undated (Box 28 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 5)
    - "Long Park Concept," Manuscript, A. Hulstrunk, Undated (Box 28 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 6)
    - "The Magic Paint of an Invisible Artist," Manuscript, V.J. Schaefer, Undated (Box 28 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 7)
    - Manuscript-- Untitled, V.J. Schaefer, Undated (Box 28 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 8)
    - Manuscript-- Untitled, V.J. Schaefer, Undated (Box 28 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 9)
    - Manuscript-- Untitled, V.J. Schaefer, Undated (Box 28 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 10)
    - Manuscript-- Untitled, V.J. Schaefer, Undated (Box 28 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 11)
    - Manuscript-- Untitled, V.J. Schaefer, Undated (Box 28 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 12)
    - "Misconception About Cloud Seeding With Dry Ice," Typescript, Anonymous, Undated (Box 28 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 13)
    - "New Field Evidence of Inadvertent Modification of the Atmosphere," Typescript and Measurements, V.J. Schaefer, Undated (Box 28 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 14)
    - "Northwestern Montana Observations," Manuscript, V.J. Schaefer, Undated (Box 28 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 15)
    - "Optimal Supplementary Research Program," Manuscript, V.J. Schaefer, Undated (Box 28 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 16)
    - "The Particulate Spectrum of Remote Areas," Reviewer's Abstract-- V.J. Schaefer, Undated (Box 28 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 17)
    - "The Presence of Certain Trace Gases in Global Air," Typescript, V.J. Schaefer, Undated (Box 28 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 18)
    - "The Presence of Ozone, Nitric Acid, and Nitrogen Dioxide in the Atmosphere," Manuscript, V.J. Schaefer, Undated (Box 28 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 19)
    - "Programs, Objectives, and Accomplishments of the Atmospheric Sciences Research Center," Typescript, V.J. Schaefer, Undated (Box 28 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 20)
    - "The Quiet Revolution," Manuscript, Anonymous, Undated (Box 28 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 21)
    - "The Region Where the Ground Trembles," Manuscript, V.J. Schaefer, Undated (Box 28 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 22)
    - "The Relationship of Trees to Atmospheric Pollution," Manuscript, V.J. Schaefer, Undated (Box 28 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 23)
    - "Research Studies at the Mount Washington Observatory," Manuscript, V.J. Schaefer, Undated (Box 28 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 24)
    - "Scientific Adventures," V.J. Schaefer, Undated (Box 28 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 25)
    - "Simple Experiments in Atmospheric Physics," V.J. Schaefer, Undated (Box 28 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 26)
    - "Snow Crystals in Fossil Form," Typescript, V.J. Schaefer, Undated (Box 28 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 27)
    - "Snowflakes: How to Identify and Preserve Them," V.J. Schaefer, Undated (Box 28 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 28)
    - "Types of Frozen Precipitation," V.J. Schaefer, Undated (Box 28 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 29)
    - Unfinished Manuscript, V.J. Schaefer, Undated (Box 28 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 30)
    - "The Vapor Method for Making Replicas of Liquid and Solid Aerosols," V.J. Schaefer, Undated (Box 28 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 31)
  - Photographs, 1946-1988; Undated; 6.8
    In addition to traditional photos, the photographs subseries also contains negatives and photo slides. Topics include the environment, chemistry, electrostatics, ice and snow, and world travel. While some of the images in this subseries are directly related to Schaefer's professional work, others are likely derived from extracurricular activities he engaged in while taking photographs for business purposes. Schaefer never did like to let an opportunity go by to explore things that were of interest to him. Some topics, like the Yellowstone Field Expedition, exist as their own subseries elsewhere. In the interests of preserving original order, however, those images were not pulled from this subseries.
    Researchers might note that the dates of this subseries span far more than Schaefer's ASRC years. Although some of the photos, slides, and negatives are from G.E., Munitalp, and consulting jobs, Schaefer certainly drew upon his past resources while working for the University at Albany/ASRC. He also stayed on in an advisory capacity after his official retirement, which is why there are images that post-date 1976.
    - AAAS Chautauqua- Photo Slides, 1952-1972 (Box 29 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 1)
    - AAAS Chautauqua- Photo Slides, 1972 (Box 29 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 2)
    - AAAS Chautauqua- Photo Slides, 1971-1972 (Box 29 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 3)
    - AAAS- Negatives, 1972 (Box 29 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 4)
    - AAAS Chautauqua- Photo Slides, 1971-1972 (Box 29 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 5)
    - Adirondacks- Negatives, Undated (Box 29 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 6)
    - Adirondacks- Negatives, Undated (Box 29 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 7)
    - Adventures Ahead- Photos, Undated (Box 29 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 8)
    - Adventures Ahead- Photo Slides, 1963-1972 (Box 29 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 9)
    - Air in Homes- Photo Slides, 1971-1976 (Box 29 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 10)
    - Air Quality- Photos, Undated (Box 29 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 11)
    - Air Quality- Photo Slides, 1950-1974 (Box 29 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 12)
    - Air Quality- Photo Slides, 1963-1972 (Box 29 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 13)
    - Air Quality- Photo Slides, 1965-1972 (Box 29 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 14)
    - Air Quality- Photo Slides, 1967-1971 (Box 29 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 15)
    - Air Quality Lecture- Photo Slides, 1966-1973 (Box 29 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 16)
    - Air Quality Station- Photos, Undated (Box 29 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 17)
    - Alaska- Photo Slides, 1973 (Box 29 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 18)
    - Along Beall Trail, Little Colorado River- Negatives, Undated (Box 29 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 19)
    - Apparati- Photos, 1975 (Box 29 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 20)
    - Arizona Expeditions- Photos, 1976 (Box 29 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 21)
    - ASRC Activities, notes, 1971 (Box 29 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 22-23)
    - ASRC Early Days- Negatives, 1966 (Box 29 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 24)
    - ASRC Faculty and Students- Photos, Undated (Box 29 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 25)
    - ASRC Hangar- Negatives, Undated (Box 29 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 26)
    - ASRC Hangar- Photos, 1962 (Box 29 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 27)
    - ASRC Hangar- Photos, Undated (Box 29 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 28-29)
    - ASRC LES- Negatives, Undated (Box 29 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 30)
    - ASRC Lake George- Negatives, Undated (Box 29 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 31)
    - ASRC New Facilities- Negatives, Undated (Box 29 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 32)
    - ASRC Research Center- Negatives and Prints, Undated (Box 29 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 33)
    - Atmospheric Optics- Photo Slides, 1948-1968 (Box 29 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 34)
    - Atmospheric Optics- Photo Slides, 1948-1976 (Box 30 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 1)
    - Atmospheric Optics- Photo Slides, 1961-1973 (Box 30 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 2)
    - Atmospheric Phenomena- Photo Slides, 1952-1964 (Box 30 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 3)
    - Atmospheric Phenomena-Photo Slides, 1952-1972 (Box 30 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 4)
    - Atmospheric Quality- Photo Slides, 1955-1972 (Box 30 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 5)
    - Atmospheric Sciences Program-ARS- Loomis-Photo Slides, 1961 (Box 30 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 6-10)
    - Atmospherics- Slides, 1947-1973 (Box 30 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 11)
    - Atmospherics- Slides, 1954-1977 (Box 30 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 12)
    - Atmospherics- Slides, 1956-1976 (Box 30 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 13)
    - Atmospherics- Early Negatives, Undated (Box 30 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 14)
    - Atmospherics- Waterfall Electricity Slides, 1965-1973 (Box 30 (6-Atmospheric Sciences Research Center), Folder 15)